Guide to the Creative Time Archive 1973-2006 MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Mail Art - Marcos Kurtycz, 107119
  - Mirror with Photo artwork, Undated; 107120 (Box 20, Folder 89)
- Oversize Series, 107084
  This series contains oversize materials from Series I, IV, VII and includes exhibition catalogues, magazines, building proposals, photographic materials (including negatives, contact sheets, and prints), blueprints, posters, and hand-drawn mock-ups for exhibition catalogue.
  - Oversize Series I: Projects, Programs and Publications, 107100
    - Janet Kardon and Paula Marincola, "Red Grooms' Philadelphia Cornucopia" (Institute of Contemporary Art, University of Pennsylvania, 1982), 107118 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - Stroll magazine, Vol. 1, No. 1 (Spring/Summer, 1985), 107117 (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - "Fragments From the Journals of Charles Cooper", intro. Jane Greengold ("A Drop in the Bucket"), 1985; 107116 (Box 21, Folder 260)
    - Stroll magazine, Vol. 2, No. 1 (Winter, 1986) [Art on the Beach feature], 107115 (Box 21, Folder 261)
    - Stroll magazine, Vol. 2, No. 2 (Nov-Jan, 1986), 107114 (Box 21, Folder 262)
    - "Honeymoon Miralda Project, 1986-1992" (Barcelona, Spain: Ambit Serveis Editorials, 1988) [2 copies], 107113 (Box 21, Folder 263)
    - Performance in the Park 1986-1987 catalogue [2 copies], 107112 (Box 21, Folder 264)
    - Battery Maritime Building Proposals - Diller and Scofidio architectural proposal; CT and Dance Theater Workshop proposal [2 items], 1988; 107111 (Box 21, Folder 265)
    - Poster - Art on the Beach, 1978; 107110 (Folder 5 Right)
    - Autograph Mock-Ups for exhibition catalogue [2 sheets] - Custom and Culture, 1979; 107109 (Folder 6 Right)
    - Blueprints - Art on the Beach, Craig S. Konyk, Eric Gould, Anthony Tsirantonakis, Jim Croak, Ken Kaplan, Ted Krueger [12 items], 1987; 107108 (Folder 12)
    - Poster - "Kissing Doesn't Kill: Greed and Indifference Do", Gran Fury, [1989]; 107107 (Folder 1 Left)
    - Posters - "Surgeon General's Warning", Beth B. [5 items], 1990; 107106 (Folder 13)
    - Blueprints - "Sacrificial Ornament", Spring Hurlbut [3 items], 1991; 107105 (Folder 11)
    - Poster - "Visualize This", Nancy Burson, [1991]; 107104 (Folder 4 Left)
    - Posters - Art on the Beach [2 items], Undated; 107103 (Folder 3 Left)
    - Posters - Art on the Beach [2 items], Undated; 107102 (Folder 2 Left)
    - Poster - Art in the Anchorage, Undated; 107101 (Folder 9 Right)
    - Facsimiles, undated (Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6)
  - Oversize Series VII: Marcos Kurtycz - Mail Art, 107085
    - Envelope art - fold-out faces print, 25 November 1988, 107090 (Folder 7 Right)
    - Envelope art - "Southwestern Fires", 1988; 107089 (Folder 10 Right)
    - "XYZOMPANTLI" performance poster, 8 December 1990, 107088 (Folder 8 Right)
    - "Organikwars Hocker" fold-out artwork, Undated; 107087 (Folder 14)